=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
Who's there?
من هناك؟
It's still early for god's sake!
ما زال الوقت مبكرا لوجه الله!
It's noon now.
الظهيرة الآن.
Ms. Xiang.
السيدة شيانغ.
It's no longer early.
لم يعد الوقت مبكرا.
Sorry.
آسف.
My phone died.
انتهي شحن هاتفي.
You cried?
بكيت؟
No.
لا.
I yawned.
تثاءبت.
Can we speak inside?
هل يمكننا التحدث بالداخل؟
Eh.
إيه.
Wait.
انتظر.
Let me get changed.
اسمحوا لي أن أتغير.
Give me a moment.
أعطني لحظة.
Sugar for your coffee?
سكر لقهوتك؟
Ms. Xiang, did you have a rough night?
السيدة شيانغ ، هل كان لديك ليلة عصيبة؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
You see nothing.
لا ترى شيئا.
Mr. Chu.
السيد.  تشو.
What can I help?
ما الذي يمكنني مساعدة؟
I need you to sign the documents
أريدك أن توقع على المستندات
from B.O. and Ruide.
من BO و Ruide.
That's all?
هذا كل شئ؟
This shouldn't require you to visit me.
هذا لا ينبغي أن يتطلب منك زيارتي.
The other party doesn't usually
الطرف الآخر لا يفعل ذلك عادة
go MIA.
اذهب MIA.
I'll sign it.
سوف أوقع عليه.
I'll sign it now.
سوف أوقع عليه الآن.
I won't waste your precious time.
لن أضيع وقتك الثمين.
Don't show your handwriting
لا تظهر خط يدك
to anyone easily from now on.
لأي شخص بسهولة من الآن فصاعدًا.
Why?
لماذا؟
Because your handwriting is different.
لأن خط يدك مختلف.
How can it be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون؟
I have seen your handwriting before.
لقد رأيت خط يدك من قبل.
Although it is similar to yours now,
على الرغم من أنه مشابه لك الآن ،
the pauses are different.
وقفات مختلفة.
Are you Xiang Wei?
هل أنت شيانغ وي؟
I am.
انا.
It can't be any clearer.
لا يمكن أن يكون أكثر وضوحا.
For real?
بصدق؟
It's quite likely that you won't
من المحتمل جدًا أنك لن تفعل ذلك
believe what I'm about to say.
أصدق ما سأقوله.
Right.
الصحيح.
You are Xiang Wei
أنت شيانغ وي
from another world
من عالم آخر
who has different memories.
من لديه ذكريات مختلفة.
Wow.
رائع.
What on earth.
ماذا على الارض.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Isn't that what you wanted to hear?
أليس هذا ما أردت أن تسمعه؟
Chu Yumo,
تشو يومو
is there sanity
هل هناك عقل
in your brain?
في دماغك؟
I believe you.
واعتقد انكم.
I believe
أعتقد
whatever you say.
أيا كان ما تقوله.
Oh.
أوه.
Now that you have signed it,
الآن بعد أن وقعت عليه ،
I should go.
يجب ان اذهب.
I'll see you off.
سأراكم.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Okay.
تمام.
If Xiang Wei comes back
إذا عاد Xiang Wei
and sees the mess I make out of her life,
وترى الفوضى التي أحدثتها في حياتها ،
she will scold me.
ستوبخني.
I need to leave something in her new life.
أحتاج إلى ترك شيء ما في حياتها الجديدة.
(Chu Yumo)
(تشو يومو)
(Ruthless Feud of A Rich Family...)
(عداء لا يرحم لعائلة غنية ...)
(Will Contest...)
(سوف تنافس ...)
Sorry.
آسف.
I think you got the wrong door.
أعتقد أنك حصلت على الباب الخطأ.
I didn't ask for janitor service.
لم أطلب خدمة بواب.
Are you Ms. Xiang?
هل أنت السيدة شيانغ؟
I am.
انا.
I am at the right place then.
أنا في المكان المناسب إذن.
Mr. Chu paid me double wages to come here.
دفع لي السيد تشو أجرًا مضاعفًا حتى أتي إلى هنا.
He even told me
حتى أنه قال لي
to spend extra effort in making sure it's clean and tidy.
لبذل المزيد من الجهد للتأكد من أنها نظيفة ومرتبة.
Chu Yumo.
تشو يومو.
Are you making fun of me?
هل تسخر مني؟
Sir.
سيد.
Someone gave you this
أعطاك شخص ما هذا
flower.
زهرة.
(Sir.)
(سيد.)
(Someone gave you this)
(شخص ما أعطاك هذا)
(flower.)
(زهرة.)
Who?
من؟
No idea.
لا أعلم.
It isn't written anywhere.
لم يكتب في أي مكان.
(No idea.)
(لا أعلم.)
(It isn't written anywhere.)
(لم يكتب في أي مكان.)
She said there was another toy
قالت كان هناك لعبة أخرى
and you would know when you opened it.
وستعرف متى قمت بفتحه.
(She said there was another toy)
(قالت كان هناك لعبة أخرى)
(and you would know when you opened it.)
(وستعرف متى فتحته.)
(Thank you,)
(شكرًا لك،)
(Momo.)
(مومو).
(Because of you,)
(بسببك،)
(my life is warm.)
(حياتي دافئة.)
(Thank you,)
(شكرًا لك،)
(Momo.)
(مومو).
(Because of you,)
(بسببك،)
(my life is warm.)
(حياتي دافئة.)
(Thank you,)
(شكرًا لك،)
(Momo.)
(مومو).
(Because of you,)
(بسببك،)
(my life is warm.)
(حياتي دافئة.)
Xiang Wei...
شيانغ وي ...
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I dealt with some company's crises from before.
لقد تعاملت مع أزمات بعض الشركات من قبل.
I feel relieved.
أشعر بالارتياح.
Are you used to your life now?
هل أنت معتاد على حياتك الآن؟
I think
أظن
some time alone
بعض الوقت بمفردك
allows me to do a lot of thinking and I found many answers.
يسمح لي بالتفكير كثيرًا ووجدت العديد من الإجابات.
My failed marriage
زواجي الفاشل
isn't all Jiang Fengyan's fault.
ليس كل خطأ جيانغ فنغيان.
I was too eager.
كنت حريصة جدا.
I asked him
لقد سالته
to give me the love
ليعطيني الحب
and hope I couldn't get from my family.
وآمل أنني لم أستطع الحصول على من عائلتي.
But the dust has settled.
لكن الغبار هدأ.
You should take a break.
يجب أن تأخذ استراحة.
But this moment of peacefulness
لكن هذه اللحظة من الهدوء
feels like
أحس كأنني
the calm before the storm.
الهدوء الذى يسبق العاصفة.
You still work as hard
ما زلت تعمل بجد
as before.
كما كان من قبل.
What about your love life?
ماذا عن حياتك العاطفية؟
I feel like... After being submerged for a long time,
أشعر وكأن ... بعد أن غمرني الماء لفترة طويلة ،
when you resurface,
عندما تعود إلى الظهور ،
you feel
أنت تشعر
breathless.
لاهث.
But after the breathlessness
ولكن بعد ضيق التنفس
is rebirth.
هو ولادة جديدة.
We play golf for three years.
نلعب الجولف لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
I didn't know a golf genius like you
لم أكن أعرف عبقري جولف مثلك
can miss her shot too.
يمكن أن تفوت تسديدتها أيضا.
It's been too long
مر وقت طويل
so I'm all rusty now.
لذلك أنا صدئة الآن.
Something's in your mind?
شيء ما في ذهنك؟
Why are you so nervous?
لماذا أنت عصبي جدا؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
Something about my work just came
شيء ما عن عملي جاء للتو
to my mind suddenly.
في ذهني فجأة.
Golfing
الجولف
is to force you to act against your nature.
هو إجبارك على التصرف ضد طبيعتك.
When we can defy
متى يمكننا التحدي
our instinct,
غريزتنا ،
we're not far away
نحن لسنا بعيدين
from the perfect serve.
من الخدمة المثالية.
After all,
بعد كل ذلك،
the soil provides a greater hindrance
توفر التربة عائقًا أكبر
than air.
من الهواء.
Don't you agree?
لا توافق؟
(In my 25 years of living,)
(خلال 25 عامًا من عيشي ،)
(I have never played golf before.)
(لم ألعب الغولف من قبل).
(Xiang Wei's world is getting more and more foreign to me.)
(أصبح عالم شيانغ وي أجنبيًا أكثر فأكثر بالنسبة لي).
Wei.
وي.
You came back so soon.
لقد عدت قريبا جدا.
Don't you want to rest longer?
ألا تريد أن تستريح لفترة أطول؟
Sigh.
تنهد.
Tell me about it.
حدثني عنها.
I am working for myself.
أنا أعمل لنفسي.
I dream every day
أحلم كل يوم
that I'm
هذا أنا
disciplining myself.
تأديب نفسي.
Wait, Wei!
انتظر وي!
Did you get the wrong breakfast?
هل حصلت على الإفطار الخاطئ؟
You're allergic to sesame seeds.
لديك حساسية من بذور السمسم.
What?
لما؟
Wei.
وي.
(Inpatient)
(مريض داخلي)
♪Time might stop♪
♪ الوقت قد يتوقف ♪
♪The bitterness from having your soul torn apart♪
مرارة تمزق روحك
♪Hard to get out♪
♪ صعب الخروج ♪
♪Of this shackle♪
من هذا القيد ♪
♪I am drowning in this cycle♪
أنا أغرق في هذه الحلقة ♪
♪How many times have I been exploited?♪
♪ كم مرة تم استغلالي؟
♪Who is responsible for the indifference♪
من المسؤول عن اللامبالاة
♪Under the neon signs?♪
♪ تحت إشارات النيون؟
♪Swallowing this bitterness time after time♪
ابتلاع هذه المرارة مرة بعد مرة
♪Who is hiding among the clouds?♪
من يختبئ بين السحاب؟
♪I float like a feather♪
♪ أسبح كالريشة ♪
♪As I land♪
♪ كما هبطت ♪
♪Amplify this rebirth, I am awakening♪
تضخيم هذه الولادة الجديدة ، أنا أستيقظ ♪
♪Life is disappearing, It's getting tougher♪
♪ الحياة تختفي ، تزداد صعوبة ♪
♪We merely passed by each other before we fell♪
"لقد مررنا ببعضنا البعض قبل أن نسقط"
♪One more time♪
♪ مرة أخرى ♪
♪Abandon the bond and the vanity♪
ترك الرابطة والغرور ♪
♪Shatter the gossip and the criticisms♪
تحطيم الثرثرة والانتقادات
♪The final silhouette♪
♪ الصورة الظلية النهائية ♪
♪Is as quiet as tonight♪
♪ هدوء الليلة